Let me introduce an open-source project called INFOGRAPHIC
This project mainly helps us generate
similar to those templates in PowerPoint
It can convert a piece of text into
such structured graphics
somewhat similar to the things we draw in our PPT
It was quite popular back then.
4000 stars
The latest version is 0.2.12.
This version is also licensed under the MIT protocol
can be used commercially for free
Let's take a look at it
It currently supports a wide variety of charts
You can see, uh
It's called the Infographic Template Library
This is mainly used for creating PPTs.
There are various types of such charts, all very visually appealing.
This is similar to a word cloud
This effect belongs to the comparison type.
There are various comparison effects.
This is also a comparative approach through inheritance
This is a four-quadrant chart
also a comparative SWOT diagram
This is the mind map hierarchical type
This is also a hierarchical tree.
This is what it calls a list list.
This is a tabular list.
This one is a bit like a dashboard.
This one is somewhat like a trend
This is a four-quadrant chart type, and this is a circular one.
This is a sequence
This is a funnel map snake sequence
This is the online time series.
The entire structure has a total of 200
There are 236 templates
and you can customize the templates within it
Its main utility is that it can integrate with large models
through JSON representation
That is similar to defining some JSON data.
define which template type you want to use
You can define things like length,
or color or style
it can then display it for you
So it's very capable of transforming a lot of our text
can be converted into PPT templates
This is very convenient
Currently, this project also supports it
This project natively supports the integration within Cloud Code
integration of skills
can be integrated with Cloud Code
enable it to generate similar graphics
Currently, we can also see this project
the define project
Currently, it is also integrating the INFORMATION GRAPHIC project.
After the integration is complete
It can also utilize large models
have it generate a variety of
these very beautiful structured graphics
If you can generate this graphic
combined with what we previously introduced to everyone
a PowerPoint template
then it can be customized to generate
various PPTs in our enterprise
Alright, let me briefly introduce this project.
written in app script
using JavaScript or TypeScript for development
It is also a frontend-oriented application.
It can also be saved as an image or vector-like graphics.
It is capable of all these.
Alright, that concludes our introduction to this project today.